♪ ♪
There, thanks.
Whew, boy, somebody
killed that old man;
they were trying to kill us.
Jack Rinaldi?
No, he wouldn't
use his own name.
Well, then it had to be someone
who knew we were
looking for them.
Vicki Mariani knew.
No.
Okay, Detective
Cox, David O'Malley...
Did, uh, did Bobby Boyd know
you were at Vicki
what's-her-name's house?
I don't think so. Why?
Well, I think,
I think it may very well
have been Bobby Boyd
and maybe some of his friends.
Thank you.
Mr. Boyd.
I heard from Jack.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Look, uh, he wanted me
to give you a message.
Okay.
Jack says that you and
your friends got two days
to put $500,000 into
his offshore account
or he'll give the
tape to the police.
Miss Mariani, we came
to pay our respects
to Sam Chandler.
Whatever you need to
discuss can wait till tomorrow.
Excuse me.
There he is.
Well, gentlemen...
Mr. Matlock, are you all right?
No. What happened?
Somebody tried to blow me and
my friend here to kingdom come.
But you didn't quite make it.
And I know that one of
you killed Sam Chandler.
I know that as good
as I'm standing here.
And I know that one of you
suckered me into going down
to that warehouse.
You may not know
it, but you killed
an innocent man.
But you were trying
to kill me, one of you.
And I'll get you for that.
Shut up, old man!
Come on, come on! Mr. Matlock,
I think you're making
a terrible mistake.
What have we done to
make you so angry at us?
One of you, or maybe
all of you, tried to kill me.
What do you think?
They did it.
I'm certain of it.
Excuse me.
I'll meet you back at the car.
Allow me.
What gave me away?
The legs.
Thank you.
Well... well, Miss Page...
I've heard a lot about you.
All bad I'm sure.
I'm gonna go home and change,
and I'll meet you at
David O'Malley's office.
I'll get fired if you tell
David you saw me.
Vicki Mariani had a little
chat with Bobby Boyd inside.
Now, I couldn't hear every word,
but it sounded like Jack Rinaldi
is blackmailing
Bobby and his friends.
Over what?
She didn't say.
Angela, didn't I tell you not
to go to that service today?
David, I was
just trying to help.
Go clean out your office.
Jessica will arrange
your severance.
I can't have employees
that don't follow instructions.
David, can't we discuss this?
Yeah, what a...
No, we cannot.
I'm sorry.
Ben!
Hey.
Let me help you with it.
Excuse me.
I feel awful.
Your boss shouldn't
have gone to David.
I told him what would happen.
I'm sorry.
And what about you?
What are you, what
are you doing here?
I don't know.
I'm saying goodbye, I guess.
You're sweet.
If you're ever up in the
city, you give me a call.
Okay, I will.
I mean it.
And I think I have
an idea of how to
find Jack Rinaldi.
Yeah? Yeah.
Uh, Vicki Mariani?
Oh, I'll sign for them.
Hi. Thanks.
Thank you.
For you.
Who are they from?
A friend.
I'd like to meet this guy.
He must be the greatest.
♪ ♪
321 Chancellor.
It'll take me about three
hours to get to Jacksonville.
You're going to
Jacksonville on a hunch?
Not a hunch.
Now who?
Hi.
My name's Jack Rinaldi.
I travel a lot and I
lost my credit card.
I'm not sure where.
I was wondering
if you could tell me
where I used the card last.
Rinaldi.
R-I-N-A-L-D-I.
Yeah, Jack.
7-4-3-3
zero-1-1-4
zero-1-4-6-8.
Where'd you get that number?
On a credit card
receipt at Vicki Mariani's.
Yeah.
Ah, that's what I thought.
Thanks a lot.
Jacksonville?
Jacksonville.
Call me when you get there.
One other thing.
I saw Detective Cox.
He has Vicki Mariani's
office building staked out.
Himself?
Yeah.
It's odd, isn't it?
Seems like he'd have
one of his men do it.
Hey, we got 40 minutes
of continuous music
from WDRN Jacksonville.
Playing rock and roll
while you're on the road.
Hi. Yes?
I'm Jackie Wilson;
I'm with the city.
What do you want?
We're checking all the
houses in the neighborhood
to see if the pipes are
insulated with asbestos.
I guess it's okay.
Well, I guess I'll
start with the kitchen.
That'll be fine.
Get up.
Come on, wake up.
How do you feel?
I feel like I've
been hit with a bat.
Why did you do that?
We saw you sneaking around.
Vicki tells me you're the guy
who was looking for
me in Atlanta. Why?
I'm investigating Sam
Chandler's murder.
What's that got to do with me?
Sit down.
Okay, sorry.
Why are you here?
Because Bobby
Boyd's looking for you.
Because you're blackmailing him
and Al Brackman
and Jim Steinbach
and it all has something to do
with Sam Chandler's murder.
You just went through a
lot of trouble for nothing.
Okay, I'll be going.
Okay.
Detective Cox, how's it going?
Hartman.
Always busy this time of year.
Yeah?
I, uh, I hear you got the Warner
Realty building staked out.
Keeping an eye on Vicki Mariani?
Yeah.
You on it yourself?
Yep.
I figure that Jack Rinaldi
might just have something to do
with that warehouse.
Yeah, he might have something
to do with Sam Chandler's death.
Whoa. We got the
right guy on that one.
Got him dead to rights.
Yeah... yeah, anything on the
burglary out at Sam Chandler's?
No, not so far.
I'll see ya. Okay.
I, uh, I hear you're a skier.
Yeah. Why, you, too?
Oh, no, I've never
been on skis in my life.
I hear you got a place out West.
A little condo.
Big dollars, I bet, huh?
You know what they say:
"Life's expensive...
then you die."
You know, Jack,
you got a problem.
I've got a problem?
Because if I found you,
chances are Bobby
Boyd will find you, too.
I'll be out of the
country in 24 hours.
You can't run from these guys.
Come back to Atlanta with me.
You're nuts.
I can get you in the
witness protection plan.
You're offering me protection?
Think about it.
See, that could be
Bobby Boyd right now.
Hi.
Uh, that'll be $12.60.
Yeah, hold on.
Give me a 20.
No way. You ordered
the pizza, you pay.
I didn't order a
pizza. Neither did I.
It said 1223 Ardel.
Yeah, well, that's the address,
but we didn't order a pizza.
I probably should call.
Would you look at this.
There's no pizza in here.
There's a gun.
Okay, get your hands
on top of your head.
Over to the table.
Move it.
Unbelievable.
Let's go. We got to take him.
No way. Jack, they're
gonna find you and kill you.
We gotta go. No, I came all
the way down here to get him.
I'm not leaving
without him... get up!
Forget it. Get up!
I go back to Atlanta,
I'm dead in 24 hours.
There's no jail, nothing
will be safe for me.
Conrad...
Okay, fine.
You got it.
Jack, you got company.
Come on, take a look.
What, I look stupid?
In about 30 seconds,
you're gonna look dead.
Come on.
Man, they work for Bobby Boyd.
Come on... out the back door.
Come on. What about you?
I got a place for
a couple of days.
So let's ask Mr. Rinaldi
the question that
brought us all here.
Hmm?
Who killed Sam Chandler?
I don't know.
You mean you won't say.
No, I mean I don't know.
And what about the blackmail?
That has nothing to
do with the murder.
What's it got to do with?
Jack, thanks to us,
Bobby Boyd's boys
are in Jacksonville
and you're not.
Yeah?
This tape is a one-way ticket
to the state pen for Bobby Boyd
and Al Brackman
and Jim Steinbach.
What's on it?
I told you, it has nothing
to do with the murder.
Bobby Boyd did not send those
guys down here to deliver the money.
I know.
Well, what are you
gonna do with the tape?
I know a detective
in the Atlanta PD.
I can give him a call.
Sure.
Why not?
Uh, Ben.
Oh, hi, Bob.
Uh, you got a minute? Yeah.
Want a hot dog?
What's up?
I guess you were right
about Detective Cox.
Yeah?
I got a source,
it's pretty good,
says Richard Cox can
thank Jim Steinbach
for his condo out West,
and a big check every year.
Did you bring him in?
Can't find him.
I know where he's gonna be.
Conrad left a message.
He's bringing Jack
Rinaldi back to Atlanta.
Gonna turn him
over to Detective Cox
at Old Hanson Road
in less than a hour.
Oh...
This isolated enough for you?
Yeah, perfect.
Detective Cox, say
hello to Jack Rinaldi
and Angela Page.
Rinaldi.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
I, uh, I've arranged,
uh, living quarters for you
outside the city.
And you will have 24-hour guards
until the witness
protection people
move you out of the state.
Sounds good to me.
Your story better be worth it.
Let's go.
Thanks. I owe you.
Ah, you set me up.
I didn't. I swear.
All right, hold it.
I'm a police officer.
Tell them to lower their guns.
Richard, it's Bob Brooks.
What the hell's
going on here, Bob?
Tell them to put
away their guns.
I want you to turn over Rinaldi.
Now, we have unconfirmed
reports that his life may be in danger.
Why haven't they
lowered their guns, huh?
Dick!
Please do what I ask.
I'm out of here. No, you're not.
Get out of there, Conrad!
What are you doing?!
I'll tell you what I'm doing.
Put your weapon on
the ground, Richard.
You see this man?
He's going in my
car with me, Bob.
And if you ever want to
see Jack Rinaldi again,
you'll let us go.
Hold your fire!
You all right?
Yeah, we're okay.
Thank God.
SAM CHANDLER:
At the rate we're going,
the union's gonna
run us out of business.
I can't deal with this anymore.
The problem is Carpenter.
Then let's eliminate
the problem.
That's one way of having
our guy running the local.
Well, the D.A.'s
gonna love this.
Who's Carpenter?
Ron Carpenter.
He was president
of the local 721 International
Brotherhood of Teamsters.
Disappeared about six years
ago, one day, without a trace.
No body, no nothing.
Just like Jimmy Hoffa.
Yep. No one knows what happened.
They will now.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna run
this over to the D.A.
But I don't see how
this helps you, Ben.
What's it got to do with
Sam Chandler's death?
I don't know.
Well, you know what they say.
What?
Ain't nothin' easy.
Well...
Well, I've gotta go.
I'll talk to you later?
All right.
She followed me.
Oh.
He didn't fire her.
I know.
Well, what do you think?
Detective Cox
killed Jack Rinaldi.
Probably planted
that bomb for us.
Yeah, yeah.
So that tape somehow
has got to be connected
with Sam Chandler's death.
Uh-huh. Okay.
Well, I can do it if you want.
Which car, sir?
It's that blue one there.
Hi, Bobby. How you doing?
What did you want to
see me about, Dave?
Take a seat.
It's about a tape.
Jack Rinaldi's tape.
Afraid I don't know
what that is, Dave.
Oh, no?
Well, it's a recording
of the meeting
you had about six years
ago with Al Brackman,
Jim Steinbach and Sam Chandler.
When the four of you planned
the murder of Ron Carpenter,
the ex-president of local 721,
of the International
Brotherhood of Teamsters.
You accusing me of murder, Dave?
I'm not.
Who is?
I guess you didn't hear.
Jack Rinaldi got himself
popped early this morning.
The Atlanta police
have that tape now.
Oh, and apparently, uh,
Al Brackman spent the
better part of the afternoon
talking with a
Lieutenant, uh, Brooks.
What's Al talking
to the police about?
Gee, I don't know, Bobby.
What do you think?
Al's setting somebody up.
Well, the word is
that Brackman told the
cops that you were the one
who set up the hit
on Ron Carpenter.
Really.
He said you were the one
who put out the contract.
That's a lie.
And you were the
one who paid it off.
I don't believe this.
Well, maybe I'm wrong.
It's just what I heard.
They do have a full-scale
investigation going,
and the word is they're
about 24 hours away
from pressing charges.
Well, that's not
going to happen.
You don't think Al
Brackman would sell you out?
You're wrong.
The man's a common criminal.
First of all, I'm a businessman.
You can skip the
disclaimers with me, Al.
Second, Bobby Boyd
and Jim Steinbach
have known me my entire life.
They know I'd never
go to the police,
and I'd never sell them out.
You've also never faced
murder one charges
before, have you, Al?
I did not go to the police.
Then tell Bobby and Jim that.
You son of a bitch.
They're your good
friends. Talk to them.
I'm sure they'll listen.
You're trying to set me up.
They'll never believe you.
Well...
Mr. Brackman,
would you excuse us?
Mr. O'Malley and I need to talk.
Can't this wait? MATLOCK: No.
He's all yours.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Don't bother.
Your secretary told me
where I could find you.
What are you going
to do, yell at me?
No.
Yeah, you're
going to yell at me.
You're going to yell
at me for investigating,
for doing what I do for a
living, which I'm damn good at.
I know the Al Brackmans of
the world a lot better than you do.
I spend my life working with
scum like that. David... David...
This close to... David!
I've made a kind of
peace with myself on this.
I know you're not
going to stay out of it.
It's against your nature.
I guessed, when
you fired Angela,
you weren't firing her.
So I'm just politely asking.
When you are gonna do something,
let me know, so we don't
get in each other's way.
Fair?
Fair.
'Cause if you keep going off on
your own, I'm gonna deck you.
Okay.
I can't drop the case
now. I'm too close.
I said okay, Ben.
Okay.
I had some thoughts
about the tape.
Well, let's hear
them. All right.
Uh, Jack Rinaldi testified
against Sam Chandler.
I know that; I represented
him in the trial... Yeah, yeah.
Well, I... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But, see, he-he could've
mentioned the tape.
But he didn't. I know he didn't.
He could've hung Sam.
Yeah, but he didn't
because he wanted to blackmail
Sam Chandler and the others.
Yeah, now, Sam was a violent,
ruthless man, and ordinarily,
he wouldn't stand
still for blackmail.
Damn right he wouldn't.
Yeah. But he had a problem.
That tape was very
dangerous to him.
But he couldn't lay a
finger on Jack Rinaldi.
No, because the
finger'd point back at him.
And that's why they had to
take Sam out first, Yeah, Sam...
so they could get
to Jack Rinaldi.
Get to Jack. That's right.
That's right. So we're
getting somewhere.
Yeah.
Uh, so where is, uh... Angela?
Uh, I have her
tailing Al Brackman.
Uh, I have Conrad
rechecking alibis,
so we're getting somewhere.
This is good. This is good.
You know, you stick with me,
and you're gonna
learn how to do this.
Uh, Mr. Boyd, you have a
brother and a sister, don't you?
Yes, I do.
And you're very
fond of both of them?
Yes.
And isn't it true
that you were friends
with the deceased, Sam Chandler?
In fact, for a while, he
even dated your sister,
Kathy Boyd.
They went out for a while.
Yeah.
And then, unless I'm mistaken,
he very abruptly cut
it off with your sister,
and she was very hurt,
and you were angry.
Yes.
Did you say anything
to Mr. Chandler?
No, I don't think so.
Why not?
Sam and I had a
business relationship.
This had nothing to do with it.
Sam Chandler
had a very powerful
political and business network
throughout the
entire state, didn't he?
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
And often, when he found
uh, particular
business opportunities,
he'd give you a piece of
the action, wouldn't he?
Sam was very good to
me that way. Yeah, yeah...
He-He brought you
into the bar business
and then allowed
you to buy him out.
And he gave you a minority share
of his trucking concern.
Fact is, you needed Sam Chandler
a lot more than he needed you.
And so, when he so
cruelly dumped your sister,
there wasn't anything
you could do about it.
That must have burned you up.
Well, uh...
This is the tape
that was taken from
Jack Rinaldi's body.
You know about this tape?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Well, if I told you that
this tape is a record
of four men, including yourself,
conspiring to murder a local
Teamsters' Union president,
and that Jack Rinaldi was
using it to blackmail you,
would you then
know about the tape?
Not at all.
You know...
I run into this kind of stuff
in cases like this...
all the time.
I guess that's why I
know where to look.
If people trip themselves up,
I ask the same
questions so often,
I kind of embarrass myself,
but here we go.
Now, Mr. Boyd, this
is a bank statement.
It's your bank statement.
See? Boyd.
Right there.
Now, look right here.
You withdrew $115,000
from your account,
just 13 days before Sam
Chandler was murdered.
And this is Jack Rinaldi's
bank statement, and see?
He deposited that same amount,
on the same day,
into his account.
Now do you know about this tape?
Objection.
Relevancy.
Relevance? It goes to motive!
Mr. Matlock... Relevance?!
Mr. Matlock.
The money... why'd
you give it to him?
I wasn't the only
one paying him.
No, there were four of you.
And that's why you were
meeting at Todd's grill that night
that my client saw you.
You were deciding whether or not
to continue paying Jack
Rinaldi, weren't you?
I refuse to answer
on the grounds that it
might incriminate me.
Sam Chandler told you not
to lay a finger on Jack Rinaldi
because everyone would
assume that he had done it
because Jack
testified against him
about that big cocaine deal.
He told you that if
anything happened
to Jack Rinaldi,
he'd come after you,
and that's what you and Al
Brackman and Jim Steinbach
were arguing with Sam
Chandler about that night,
weren't you?
Did Al Brackman tell you this?
What difference does it make?
Weren't you?
Al Brackman and Jim Steinbach
have the same motive as me.
Why don't you go after them?
Because they have one
thing you don't have...
An alibi for the time Sam
Chandler was murdered.
What are you talking about?
I told you.
I was in bed with my
girlfriend that morning...
Renee Thorton.
But that's not true, is it?
This is a traffic
ticket for speeding,
issued at 6:30 a.m.
the morning Sam
Chandler was murdered.
Now, do you recognize
the signature at the bottom?
Mr. Boyd?
It's Renee's signature.
Now, unless Miss Thorton
can be in two places at once,
I think you're mistaken about
being with her that morning.
Where was she?
Where the hell were you?
The larger and more relevant
question is, where were you?
I was with a friend.
What's your friend's name?
I can't tell you that.
Your Honor, instruct
the witness to answer.
Guess it doesn't matter.
Cops tailed me there, anyway.
I was with Pedro Cruz.
Pe...
The Pedro Cruz?
Drugs?!
Yeah.
We were having breakfast.
I guess, uh, I should
call a couple of narcs
as alibi witnesses, huh?
I'll be damned.
Nothing further.
Well...
we got him on conspiracy.
We know he's one of the group
that did in that union leader.
Now we got him on dope.
We didn't get him on
Sam Chandler though.
No.
We'll have to get
somebody else on that.
SAM CHANDLER:
At the rate we're going,
the union's gonna
run us out of business.
I can't deal with this anymore.
The problem is Carpenter.
I'm gonna know this
tape by heart pretty soon.
There's got to be
something there.
We should bring someone in.
Could our guy get
Carpenter's schedule?
No problem.
Why don't we see if there's
any good opportunities
in the next couple weeks.
What is it?
You know, every time
I listen to this tape,
I think something's wrong.
Yeah?
I've listened and I've listened.
And you know what it is?
It's not what's on the tape,
it's what's not on the tape.
Well...
Now at least I know
who we're looking for.
Now, this is the much-
talked-about audio tape
recorded at a
meeting six years ago.
Are you aware there's a
conversation on this tape
about the murder
of Ron Carpenter
of Local 721 of the Teamsters?
Yes, I am.
And the Atlanta police
department questioned you
about this cassette,
didn't they?
Yes, sir.
They wanted to know if I had
any knowledge of
Mr. Carpenter's death.
And did you?
No, sir, I did not.
Huh.
You know, that's strange,
because, uh, Bobby Boyd
indicated that you were
at that meeting six years ago,
where the murder of Ron
Carpenter was discussed.
Mr. Boyd's memory is mistaken.
Mm-hmm.
I wasn't at that meeting.
Oh! Oh, oh...
Well... Oh, well,
that explains it.
Explain what?
Well, Bobby Boyd
and Jim Steinbach
were both being
blackmailed by Jack Rinaldi,
and they assumed
that you were, too,
but your voice is-is nowhere
to be found on this tape.
I wasn't at that meeting.
Yeah.
Uh, so you were
not being blackmailed
by Jack Rinaldi?
No, sir, I was not.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Well, uh...
you know, that brings
up an odd question.
Uh, if-if Sam Chandler
and Bobby Boyd
and Jim Steinbach were
the only ones at that meeting,
who made the tape?
I mean, certainly
not one of them.
I haven't the faintest idea.
Huh.
There's something else,
something else strange
about this tape, too.
If you listen to it carefully,
there are some, like,
inappropriate pauses.
And-And sometimes
the conversation
doesn't, doesn't flow.
And sometimes you'll
hear a little, kinda little
little glitch, you know.
So, uh, I had this tape
analyzed by an
expert, and, uh...
Yeah.
It's been edited.
The tape's been edited.
And this expert is
prepared to testify
that somebody who really
knew what he was doing
spent a lot of
time on this tape.
Now, Mr. Brackman,
would you have any idea
who had the tape edited?
No, I do not.
Oh.
But you did know
Jack Rinaldi? Yes, I did.
He worked for your
father ten years ago,
didn't he? Yes.
He also worked for Sam
Chandler and Bobby Boyd.
Oh, who was he working for
when he testified
against Sam Chandler?
The police.
I think he was working for you.
And I think you
were at that meeting.
And I think you edited
your voice off this tape.
And I think that Jack
Rinaldi was working for you,
because you were the only one
who could give him
this tape, weren't you?
Objection.
Relevancy.
Does it really matter
who he was employed by?
It matters a lot!
Mr. Matlock.
It matters a lot! Mr. Matlock.
It matters a lot!
Sustained.
All right, let's go at this
from a different direction.
Who was Arthur Samosa?
He was a very
dear friend of mine.
D-Deceased?
He, uh, died about ten
years ago, in a freak accident.
Was a bomb under the
hood of the car, wasn't it?
That was the
speculation at the time.
Well, whose car was he driving?
My father's.
What was he doing
in your father's car?
He was bringing it
around front to my father.
Oh!
So we can assume
that bomb was meant
for your father, can't we?
Did you ever find
out who put it there?
No.
Hmm.
You know, things
were very different
in Atlanta ten years ago.
There was a real struggle
over control of
drugs in the city.
And your father appeared
to be emerging as the winner.
Until that bomb.
And then the newspapers
were all full of speculation
that Bobby Boyd
or Jim Steinbach
or Sam Chandler
was responsible.
My father never believed
that, and neither did I.
Oh, I believe so.
Just stands to reason.
You and your father had to
know that, if you retaliated,
there'd be an all-out war.
So he waited...
and he waited, and you waited,
until you could
not be implicated
in Ron Carpenter's murder.
And then you edited this tape
and gave it to Jack Rinaldi.
And he used excerpts
to blackmail the others.
And then...
when the time came,
and you knew where he would be
and you knew he would be alone,
you killed Sam Chandler.
I was sleeping with my wife
the morning Sam
Chandler was killed.
You can call her to the
stand and she'll testify to it.
Yeah, I know she would.
Your wife loves you very much.
Uh...
You wear a-a
medical alert bracelet
because you're
allergic to penicillin.
Yes, I do.
You have it on now
and you wear it always?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
The, uh...
the autopsy...
on, uh, Sam Chandler...
says... that the index finger
on his right hand was broken
at the time of death.
Did you know that?
No, I did not know that.
Yeah, yeah.
And according to several
tests by the medical examiner,
it was determined that
that finger was broken
shortly before
Mr. Chandler died.
But no one's able to determine
how it was broken.
Um...
You remember that day
you and I met in the park,
you know, out by Travel
Town, by the trains?
Oh, yes, I do.
Yeah.
You were, you were, uh,
you were wearing your, uh,
medical alert
bracelet at that time?
Of course.
No, you weren't.
See?
Where did you get those?
Well, I took several of
these pictures for you,
if you remember.
Remember?
Oh, and this morning, when,
uh, when you left the house,
the police arrived
with a warrant,
and they got these
pictures for me.
And, as you can see,
you are not wearing
your bracelet.
See, there's a blowup.
Why not?
I-I don't know.
Did you break it?
I-I-I forget.
How?
I-I-I don't, I don't remember.
Do you know where you broke it?
No, I d-d...
What difference does it make?!
Well...
Here's a gentleman...
Mr. Vincent Maretta.
You recognize him?
He will testify
that he repaired the clasp
on your bracelet.
And it appeared to
him that someone had
torn that clasp apart,
as if it were ripped
right off your arm.
And I think that's
what happened.
When you shot Sam Chandler,
he knew it was you; he saw you.
He knew about the
bracelet; he saw it.
Just before he died, he grabbed
it and ripped it off your arm
in hopes it would
identify you as his killer.
And that's how
he broke his finger.
And that's why...
you're not wearing your
bracelet in these pictures.
Now...
ladies and gentlemen,
that may not be sufficient
proof for an indictment.
But it is sufficient to cast
a reasonable doubt
as to the guilt of my client.
And it's enough
for the good officers
of the Atlanta police department
to launch an investigation.
And when they do,
I'm sure they'll find
that you were not
at home with your wife that day.
You were somewhere else.
They'll find somebody
who saw you
headed out toward Sam's place,
maybe heard the shot,
maybe saw you going back again.
Pretty soon,
you'll find yourself
back in here.
Only you won't be sitting there,
you'll be sitting over there...
in hopes someone can defend you.
Nothing further.
Have you reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
We find the defendant,
David O'Malley,
not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury.
This court stands adjourned.
Here they come.
Mr. Matlock, can I have
some photos, please?
Shake my hand. Hmm?
Shake my hand.
Oh. Thank you, Ben.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, Mr. O'Malley.
Were you worried?
With Ben Matlock
representing me? Never.
You never thought about
taking over your own defense?
Not for a minute.
This man's the best.
I would never consider
trying to second-guess him.
Want to go to
Templin's to celebrate?
Yeah. What do you think?
What's Templin's?
It's a bar. Right?
It's got music and drinks
Mmm! And good food.
And there's a booth in the
back that's good for us and...
Oh!
And they can sit in front.
Of course.
www.tvsubtitles.net